cotopaxi.com 2017-02-17

# Privacy Policy – Cotopaxi

Cotopaxi is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors of this web site and registered users. At Cotopaxi, we want you to have an enjoyable shopping experience. And while it is necessary for us to collect certain personal information, which you consent to collect by accessing or registering on this web site, we respect and protect your right to privacy as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

###### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site Privacy Policy.

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, graduation year, gender, mailing address or credit card information. While you may visit our site anonymously, if you do not provide the requested information, you may not be able to access or use some of the features and functions of our web site and we may not be able to provide you with certain services.

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

* To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).
* To process transactions (your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested).
* To send you marketing materials (the email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.). We may combine the information we collect with data from third party sources. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future correspondence, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or you may contact customer service to opt out of receiving marketing materials.

How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

Except as part of a sale of the Company or the majority of assets of the Company, we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, creating marketing materials, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to comply with this privacy policy and therefore keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. If you are not 13 or older, you are not authorized to use this site. If we learn that a user is under 13 years of age, we will promptly delete any Personal Information we have collected about that user.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the date hereunder. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. Your continued use of the website constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions. This policy was last modified on 04/09/2014.
